linux-archive.org 2017-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Your Security is Our Mission

Our privacy policy discloses our conditions for your personal information and privacy.

**Gathering information  
**  
We gather following information from users :  
a) registration information for participating in forums and newsletter subscription  
b) Information required to post comments.  
Email addresses provided in appropriate fields will not be disclosed to third party except when required by law. We can not protect your data if you enter it in fields designated for public display like forum posts or comment posts text.  
We use analytics packages for improving our site and troubleshooting various problems.  
a) Google Analytics. You can download google analytics opt-out tool here http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout if you have problems with that. Google analytics uses cookies.  
b) server logs, like almost any website in the world.

**Cookies  
**  
Linux-archive.org might use session cookies to allow you access to specific features of the site that requires being logged in (e.g. forum).  
Linux-archive.orgshows advertisements and 3-rd party content, which might use cookies for providing best value to our visitors. This includes, but is not limited to:  
a) AddThis  
b) Google Adsense/DFP and Kontera for displaying advertisements through networks.  
c) Affiliate networks to attribute software downloads (element5, cleverbridge.com, onenetworkdirect.com,cj.com and some other networks).  
d) Analytics packages, covered above.  
This is done to identify visitor arival source or provide customized browsing experience. We are not responsible for the information they collect. If you want to avoid this, you can disable cookies or allow them one by one. Some of our offered discounts might be void if user disables cookies, as the discounts might be offered for our readers only.

**Data protection and using the data  
**

Thought there are cases when we can not provide safety for aggregate or personally identifiable information. This statement is about your aggregate information that is left for your responsibility to publicize it or not. We do not take responsibility for information safety and privacy that you post in public on our web site or send it by e-mail to others members of site community. We also are not responsible for illegally disclosed aggregate information from third parties.

Note that we can disclose your aggregate information to third parties, but only if we consider this necessary and with conditions that this would be with your knowledge for certain third parties. It may be disclosed for government or juridical institutions if we find it necessary.

The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us. We ensure implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access and improper use. But note that despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.  
There is a small possibility that we might sell or merge with another business. In such ceses the information we gathered (aka Google Analytics data, comment information we have stored, server logs and other information) might be among transfered assets.

**Linked sites and advertisements  
**

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site.Â Linux-archive.org expects all linked sites to respect privacy of its users. Be aware, that third parties may have their own privacy and data collection policy.Â Linux-archive.org is not responsible for actions or policies of any other site. Some of advertisers might collect information in order to determine if you have seen the advertisement before, or in other ways to improve your experience.

**Site Use  
**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
